<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hurricane Shark</title><link>https://hurricaneshark.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Hurricane Shark</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 17:43:02 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hurricaneshark.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>43rd IEEE Symposium on Security and Privacy, Day One</title><link>https://hurricaneshark.github.io/posts/2022-05-25-43rd-ieee-symposium-security-privacy-day-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 17:43:02 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://hurricaneshark.github.io/posts/2022-05-25-43rd-ieee-symposium-security-privacy-day-one/</guid><description>Attended the first day of the 43rd IEEE Symposium on Security and Privacy (website) for my day job&amp;hellip; by which I mean I finally got around to watching the recordings for the first day, two days later. Virtual conferences are a wonderful thing. Figured I&amp;rsquo;d write about it here, partially because it&amp;rsquo;s relevant, and partially because I&amp;rsquo;m expecting a bean counter at my day job six months from now to order me to prove I really did &amp;ldquo;virtually attend&amp;rdquo; it.</description></item><item><title>Adding Plausible Analytics to Website</title><link>https://hurricaneshark.github.io/posts/2022-05-25-adding-plausible-analytics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 15:34:22 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://hurricaneshark.github.io/posts/2022-05-25-adding-plausible-analytics/</guid><description>Added Plausible Analytics (plausible.io) to the website last night. Debated if I should make a post about it, figured that I might as well in case anyone accuses me of having &amp;ldquo;secret&amp;rdquo; trackers in the future.
Out of all the options I looked into, Plausible and Matomo were the two strongest privacy-focused trackers that offered both free roll-your-own (if I ever choose to go the self-hosted route again) and paid cloud versions.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Apocalypse CTF 2022 Results</title><link>https://hurricaneshark.github.io/posts/2022-05-21-cyber-apocalypse-ctf-2022-results/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 14:24:06 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://hurricaneshark.github.io/posts/2022-05-21-cyber-apocalypse-ctf-2022-results/</guid><description>Attended my first CTF, &amp;ldquo;Cyber Apocalypse CTF 2022&amp;rdquo;, which was put on by HackTheBox. The theming was a bit&amp;hellip; odd but overall it was fun. Contributed the most to the crypto challenges, which was one of the categories I least expected to be useful for, as memories of classwork from ten years ago started flooding back in.
My team consisted of other first timers from work trying to satisfy security certification requirements.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://hurricaneshark.github.io/posts/2022-05-21-hello-world/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 11:18:14 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://hurricaneshark.github.io/posts/2022-05-21-hello-world/</guid><description>Writing this from a coffee shop in the heart of Manhattan, far from home.
Hopefully this website will last longer than my last one, running a webserver from a Raspberry Pi in your closet may be worth the geek cred as long as you let a certain monolithic corporation manage your DNS entries automagically, but once you&amp;rsquo;ve migrated to a different provider, playing Whack-A-Mole with dynamic DNS entries isn&amp;rsquo;t worth it.</description></item></channel></rss>